<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RaccoonMovie</string>
    <string name="Dogma_text">
        Two fallen angels Loki and Bartleby, doomed to forever hang around in Wisconsin,
        learn that they have a chance to return to paradise.
        To do this, you just need to use the Catholic dogma,
        hailed as a pioneering cardinal: everyone who passes through a consecrated arch in a cathedral in New Jersey
        receives remission of sins.
    </string>
    <string name="MNB_text">

    The last film from the lyrical triptych of Alexei Balabanov.
    Three friends stand on the threshold of a luxurious house in the center of a big city.
    They are young, full of strength and energy, they have talent, skill, lust for life and...
    - in general, they have everything except one. Except money.
    However, for this they came here - to offer the services of a designer to the hostess of the house.
    Natella Antonovna is also young, but it seems that life has already bored her.
    </string>

    <string name="Pl_text">

     David Wagner is a child of the nineties.
        But he is fascinated by the television show Pleasantville, which takes place in the 50s.
        in a small town of the same name, where everyone is chic, cheerful and pure,
        and life is wonderfully pleasant.
    </string>


    <string name="Coven_text">

      The third season of American Horror Story is about a coven of witches,
        disguised as an elite boarding house for "gifted" girls,
        who is trying to protect the last representatives of this species from extinction.
    </string>

    <string name="St_text">

      This squadron became "singing" - this is how Captain Titarenko selected newcomers for himself.
        His "old men" were no more than twenty, but the "yellow mouths"
        replenishment from the flight schools of the accelerated release, into battle anyway,
        If possible, they were not allowed.
        They still had a lot to experience - both the heat of battles, and the joy of the first victory over the enemy,
        and the greatness of the brotherhood, sealed with blood, and the first love, and the bitterness of loss ...
        And the day will come when, on command, “only old men go into battle”
        former yellowmouths will rush to their planes.
    </string>

    <string name="TS_text">

      Imagine that you suddenly begin to understand that everything around you is a scenery,
        and people are actors pretending to be what they seem to you.
        Your whole world turns out to be a big TV series where you play the main role,
        without even knowing it. Your whole life is the result of the work of the author of the TV show,
        which the whole planet has been watching for thirty years, starting from the moment you were born.
    </string>

    <string name="dogma">Dogma</string>
    <string name="mne_ne_bolno">Mne ne bolno</string>
    <string name="coven">Coven</string>
    <string name="plesantville">Plesantville</string>
    <string name="stariki">V boy idut odni stariki</string>
    <string name="truman">Truman`s show</string>
    <string name="button_show_favorites">Show favorites</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_title">Exit confirmation</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_message">Are you sure you want to exit</string>
    <string name="button_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="button_no">No</string>
    <string name="button_add_movie">Add</string>

</resources>